{"data":[{"question":"Count ________ one ________ one hundred, please.","a":"on \/ to","b":"to \/ on","c":"from \/ to","d":"to \/ to","answer":"3","explain":"\n- From... to: used to mention the two ends of a range.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Tom is ________ engineer.","a":"the","b":"an","c":"a","d":"one","answer":"2","explain":"\n- When mentioning career of someone, we say: he\/she... is a\/an + career.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"There is ________ ink - pot on the desk.","a":"the","b":"a","c":"an","d":"some","answer":"3","explain":"\n- There is a\/ an + noun ( an ink pot)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"What is ________ color of your pen?","a":"the","b":"a","c":"an","d":"any","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The: used before a noun that's mentioned already","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Kate and Mary are going to ________ cinema.","a":"the","b":"a","c":"an","d":"no article","answer":"1","explain":"- Go to the cinema = see a movie in the theater","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"My parents are always at ________ home on Sundays.","a":"the","b":"a","c":"an","d":"no article","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We often say stay at home","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"What's ________ weather like in winter in your country?","a":"the","b":"a","c":"an","d":"no article","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The: used to refer to something that everyone knows because it is part of our natural environment or part of daily life.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Please, put these pencils in ________ box.","a":"an","b":"the","c":"a","d":"no article","answer":"2","explain":"\n-The: used to show that you are talking about a particular thing or person that has already been mentioned, is already known about, or is the only one.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Listen to ________ teacher, please. Don't talk in class.","a":"the","b":"a","c":"an","d":"no article","answer":"1","explain":"\n-The: used to show that you are talking about a particular thing or person that has already been mentioned, is already known about, or is the only one.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"After dinner, I always wash ________ dishes.","a":"an","b":"a","c":"the","d":"no article","answer":"3","explain":"\n - A\/an + singular noun.\u00a0\n- The + definite noun.\u00a0\n- In this case, the speaker already have in mind the dishes they need to wash.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"}]}